This is tough. Our business suffered a serious blow here.
The truth is, we still have not processed it.
This is an event on a scale that is hard for us to even comprehend.
We invested our essence here, everything we could.
We put a lot of love into this. Every board that came out of here was love.
We did this out of values of Hebrew labor,
of the Land of Israel, of the people of Israel.
Our whole lives are here, truly. This is our baby
and our lives are truly here.
All the goods behind me that were left are orders for farms, for hilltop communities...
Everything is made with Hebrew labor, with love for the craft and with manual work.
We really feel a small taste of the destruction of the Temple.
We will rise up, we will succeed, and we will grow stronger,
and we will continue to hold on to the Land of Israel.
And we believe that we will come out of this stronger and greater.
Only the people of Israel are the support that gives us strength. Thank you.
Thank you very much to the entire people of Israel, for the partnership and for this warm embrace,
it truly warms the heart.